[{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "The Equity Theory of Motivation was developed by ______ in the 1960s.",
    "answer": "John Adams"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "According to Equity Theory, __________ refers to the balance between what an employee puts into their job and what they get out of it.",
    "answer": "equity"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Inputs in Equity Theory include contributions like _______, effort, skills, education, and loyalty.",
    "answer": "time"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Outcomes in Equity Theory can include rewards like _______, recognition, job security, and promotions.",
    "answer": "salary"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The perception of fairness in Equity Theory can vary from person to person based on __________.",
    "answer": "subjective experiences"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "A person feeling under-rewarded inequity happens when they perceive their _______ are greater than the outcomes they receive.",
    "answer": "inputs"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Over-rewarded inequity occurs when an individual perceives their ______ are greater than their actual inputs.",
    "answer": "outcomes"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The formula for Equity in Equity Theory is:  ( frac{O_p}{I_p} =  frac{O_a}{I_a} ), where  (Op ) stands for _______ and  (Ip ) stands for ________ for the person.",
    "answer": "outcomes, inputs"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The reference person or group in Equity Theory can include coworkers, colleagues from other organizations, or even an individual's own past experiences (known as ________).",
    "answer": "self"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "When employees feel that their inputs and outputs are not balanced, they may experience __________, leading to dissatisfaction.",
    "answer": "inequity"
  }
]
